David Locke Papers MS122
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Dagomba Dance Drumming materials, 1989 -- 2010; MS122.002; 788 Digital Object(s)
  - Jerigu, solo dance, 1999 -- 2010; MS122.002.015; 26 Digital Object(s)
    - Jerigu N-Dari O Salima lead gung-gong vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.015.00013; Locke, David
    - Jerigu N-Dari O Salima lead gung-gong drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.015.00014; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Jerigu N-Dari O Salima lead gung-gong drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.015.00015; Locke, David
    - Jerigu N-Dari O Salima lead gung-gong drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.015.00016; Locke, David
    - Jerigu N-Dari O Salima ensemble rhythm notation, 2010; MS122.002.015.00017; Locke, David
    - Jerigu N-Dari O Salima drumming ensemble audio, live, 2008; MS122.002.015.00018; Agbekor Drum and Dance Society, Dagomba Section; Goldmann, Jonathan
    - Jerigu N-Dari O Salima drumming ensemble audio, multitrack aggregate, 2005; MS122.002.015.00019; Lunna, Abubakari; Wasserman, Luke
    - Jerigu N-Dari O Salima lead lunga vocables transcription, 2010; MS122.002.015.00020; Locke, David
    - Jerigu lead lunga drum language audio (1) kulili bagga ni kulga negla dapala, 2010; MS122.002.015.00021; Locke, David
    - Jerigu lead lunga drum language audio (2) jerigu n-dari o salima, 2010; MS122.002.015.00022; Locke, David
    - Jerigu lead lunga drum language audio (3) gnunda bi yo ku landa, 2010; MS122.002.015.00023; Locke, David
    - Jerigu lead lunga drum language audio (4) kulili bagga nela la, 2010; MS122.002.015.00024; Locke, David
    - Jerigu lead lunga drum language audio (5) gbunbii leli m-bala la, 2010; MS122.002.015.00025; Locke, David
    - Jerigu answer lunga drum language audio (1) yendan n-dari jilima, 2010; MS122.002.015.00026; Locke, David
  - Jenkuno, solo dance, 2001 -- 2010; MS122.002.016; 25 Digital Object(s)
    Jenkuno is the appellation of M-ba Dogu Sheni, a key figure in the court of the Naa Abudu Satan. Dogu Sheni was exploiting his position as the intermediary to the paramount chief to collect excessive fees from visiting sub-chiefs, which led the sub-chiefs to avoid him when going to see the paramount chief. The drum language talks about mice sneaking by a sleeping cat, which is a warning to both the Dogu and to the sub-chiefs who were violating tradition by going around his back to see the paramount chief.
    - Story of Jenkuno, appellation for M-ba Dugu Sheni, 2002; MS122.002.016.00001; Locke, David; Lunna, Abubakari
      Told by Abubakari Lunna on May 7, 1991, and March 29, 2002. Describes how the Jenkuno rhythm is played. It is played for Dugu Sheni, an official in the court of the chief.
    - Jenkuno lead lunga vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.016.00002; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Jenkuno lead lunga vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.016.00003; Locke, David
    - Jenkuno lead lunga drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.016.00004; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Jenkuno lead lunga drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.016.00005; Locke, David
    - Jenkuno lead lunga drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.016.00006; Locke, David
    - Jenkuno answer lunga vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.016.00007; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Jenkuno answer lunga vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.016.00008; Locke, David
    - Jenkuno answer lunga drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.016.00009; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Jenkuno answer lunga drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.016.00010; Locke, David
    - Jenkuno answer lunga drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.016.00011; Locke, David
    - Jenkuno lead gung-gong vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.016.00012; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Jenkuno lead gung-gong vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.016.00013; Locke, David
    - Jenkuno lead gung-gong drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.016.00014; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Jenkuno lead gung-gong drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.016.00015; Locke, David
    - Jenkuno lead gung-gong drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.016.00016; Locke, David
    - Jenkuno ensemble rhythm notation, 2010; MS122.002.016.00017; Locke, David
    - Jenkuno drumming ensemble audio, live, 2008; MS122.002.016.00018; Agbekor Drum and Dance Society, Dagomba Section; Goldmann, Jonathan
    - Jenkuno drumming ensemble audio, multitrack aggregate, 2005; MS122.002.016.00019; Lunna, Abubakari; Wasserman, Luke
    - Jenkuno lead lunga drum language audio (1) Jenkuno, 2010; MS122.002.016.00020; Locke, David
    - Jenkuno lead lunga drum language audio (2) mani dimi ni jenkuno o gbiya, 2010; MS122.002.016.00021; Locke, David
    - Jenkuno lead lunga drum language audio (3a) m-kpee nye ma turi zung ku gba ma, 2010; MS122.002.016.00022; Locke, David
    - Jenkuno lead lunga drum language audio (3b) m-kpee nye ma turi zung ku gba ma, 2010; MS122.002.016.00023; Locke, David
    - Jenkuno lead lunga drum language audio (4) jenkuno jenkuno o gbihiya, 2010; MS122.002.016.00024; Locke, David
    - Jenkuno answer lunga drum language audio (1) shela jenkuno ni, 2010; MS122.002.016.00025; Locke, David
  - Sangmari Gong, solo dance, 1999 -- 2010; MS122.002.017; 29 Digital Object(s)
    Sanmarigon is the appellation for Naa Abudu-bla. After his father, Naa Mahama-bla, passed away, there were problems deciding who should be the regent, and later, the new Yaa-naa. Naa Abudu-bla kept a low profile as a child to avoid the jealousy of Mion-lana Tori Buni, who contested him for the chieftaincy after his father's funeral. Sanmarigon is a poetic appellation, and refers to the fact that it was Naa Abudu-bla's destiny to become Yaa-Naa, though he would have people trying to stand in his way.
    - Story of Sangmari Gong, appellation of Naa Abudu-bla, 1999; MS122.002.017.00001; Locke, David; Lunna, Abubakari
      Told by Abubakari Lunna on March 15, 1999. Edited by David Locke. Describes the Sanmari rhythm that tells story of how Naa Abudu-bla became chief.
    - Sangmari Gong lead lunga vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.017.00002; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Sangmari Gong lead lunga vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.017.00003; Locke, David
    - Sangmari Gong lead lunga drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.017.00004; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Sangmari Gong lead lunga drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.017.00005; Locke, David
    - Sangmari Gong lead lunga drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.017.00006; Locke, David
    - Sangmari Gong answer lunga vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.017.00007; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Sangmari Gong answer lunga vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.017.00008; Locke, David
    - Sangmari Gong answer lunga drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.017.00009; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Sangmari Gong answer lunga drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.017.00010; Locke, David
    - Sangmari Gong answer lunga drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.017.00011; Locke, David
    - Sangmari Gong lead gung-gong vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.017.00012; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Sangmari Gong lead gung-gong vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.017.00013; Locke, David
    - Sangmari Gong lead gung-gong drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.017.00014; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Sangmari Gong lead gung-gong drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.017.00015; Locke, David
    - Sangmari Gong lead gung-gong drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.017.00016; Locke, David
    - Sangmari Gong ensemble rhythm notation, 2010; MS122.002.017.00017; Locke, David
    - Sangmari Gong drumming ensemble audio, live, 2008; MS122.002.017.00018; Agbekor Drum and Dance Society, Dagomba Section; Goldmann, Jonathan
    - Sangmari Gong drumming ensemble audio, multitrack aggregate, 2005; MS122.002.017.00019; Lunna, Abubakari; Wasserman, Luke
    - Sangmari Gong lead lunga drum language audio (1) Kurigu dapala, 2010; MS122.002.017.00020; Locke, David
    - Sangmari Gong lead lunga drum language audio (2a) kurigu dapala Abulai bila, 2010; MS122.002.017.00021; Locke, David
    - Sangmari Gong lead lunga drum language audio (2b) kurigu kurigu dapala Abulai bila, 2010; MS122.002.017.00022; Locke, David
    - Sangmari Gong lead lunga drum language audio (3a) zhiri lagim kogiga yelmangli n-dagari, 2010; MS122.002.017.00023; Locke, David
    - Sangmari Gong lead lunga drum language audio (3b) zhiri lagim kogiga yelmangli n-dagari, 2010; MS122.002.017.00024; Locke, David
    - Sangmari Gong lead lunga drum language audio (4) Abulai Nawuni kulsa, 2010; MS122.002.017.00025; Locke, David
    - Sangmari Gong lead lunga drum language audio (5) tikuma puhivari n-libgi dakabiriba, 2010; MS122.002.017.00026; Locke, David
    - Sangmari Gong lead lunga drum language audio (6) ninsalini zagisi sheli Naawuni pihi maanda, 2010; MS122.002.017.00027; Locke, David
    - Sangmari Gong lead lunga drum language audio (7) sangmari gong Naawuni kulsa, 2010; MS122.002.017.00028; Locke, David
    - Sangmari Gong answer lunga drum language audio (1) sangmari gong sanmari gong sanmari gong ku zini tingna zheya, 2010; MS122.002.017.00029; Locke, David
  - Nawuni Mali Kpam Pam, invocation, 2001 -- 2010; MS122.002.018; 7 Digital Object(s)
    - Nawuni Mali Kpam Pam lead lunga vocable audio, 2001; MS122.002.018.00001; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Nawuni Mali Kpam Pam lead lunga vocable notation, 2010; MS122.002.018.00002; Locke, David
    - Nawuni Mali Kpam Pam lead lunga drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.018.00003; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Nawuni Mali Kpam Pam lead lunga drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.018.00004; Locke, David
    - Nawuni Mali Kpam Pam lunga drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.018.00005; Locke, David
    - Naawuni Mali Kpam drum language audio, 2010; MS122.002.018.00006; Locke, David
    - Naawuni Mali Kpam Pam drumming ensemble audio, live, 2008; MS122.002.018.00007; Agbekor Drum and Dance Society, Dagomba Section; Goldmann, Jonathan
  - Jebo, invocation, 2001 -- 2010; MS122.002.019; 7 Digital Object(s)
    - Jebo lead gung-gong vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.019.00001; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Jebo lead gung-gong vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.019.00002; Locke, David
    - Jebo lead gung-gong drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.019.00003; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Jebo lead gung-gong drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.019.00004; Locke, David
    - Jebo drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.019.00005; Locke, David
    - Jebo drumming ensemble audio, live, 2008; MS122.002.019.00006; Agbekor Drum and Dance Society, Dagomba Section; Goldmann, Jonathan
    - Jebo with lunsi drumming ensemble audio, live, 2008; MS122.002.019.00007; Agbekor Drum and Dance Society, Dagomba Section; Goldmann, Jon
  - Damba, festival dance, 2001 -- 2010; MS122.002.020; 51 Digital Object(s)
    - Damba Sochendi lead lunga vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.020.00001; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Damba Sochendi lead lunga vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.020.00002; Locke, David
    - Damba Sochendi lead lunga drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.020.00003; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Damba Sochendi lead lunga drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.020.00004; Locke, David
    - Damba Sochendi lead lunga drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.020.00005; Locke, David
    - Damba Sochendi answer lunga vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.020.00006; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Damba Sochendi answer lunga vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.020.00007; Locke, David
    - Damba Sochendi answer lunga drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.020.00008; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Damba Sochendi answer lunga drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.020.00009; Locke, David
    - Damba Sochendi answer lunga drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.020.00010; Locke, David
    - Damba Sochendi lead gung-gong vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.020.00011; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Damba Sochendi lead gung-gong vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.020.00012; Locke, David
    - Damba Sochendi lead gung-gong drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.020.00013; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Damba Sochendi lead gung-gong drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.020.00014; Locke, David
    - Damba Sochendi lead gung-gong drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.020.00015; Locke, David
    - Damba Sochendi ensemble rhythm notation, 2010; MS122.002.020.00016; Locke, David
    - Damba Sochendi drumming ensemble audio, live, 2008; MS122.002.020.00017; Agbekor Drum and Dance Society, Dagomba Section; Goldmann, Jonathan
    - Damba Sochendi drumming ensemble audio, multitrack aggregate, 2005; MS122.002.020.00018; Lunna, Abubakari; Wasserman, Luke
    - Damba Mangli lead lunga vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.020.00019; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Damba Mangli lead lunga vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.020.00020; Locke, David
    - Damba Mangli lead lunga drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.020.00021; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Damba Mangli lead lunga drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.020.00022; Locke, David
    - Damba Mangli lead lunga drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.020.00023; Locke, David
    - Damba Mangli answer lunga vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.020.00024; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Damba Mangli answer lunga vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.020.00025; Locke, David
    - Damba Mangli answer lunga drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.020.00026; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Damba Mangli answer lunga drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.020.00027; Locke, David
    - Damba Mangli answer lunga drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.020.00028; Locke, David
    - Damba Mangli lead gung-gong vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.020.00029; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Damba Mangli lead gung-gong vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.020.00030; Locke, David
    - Damba Mangli lead gung-gong drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.020.00031; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Damba Mangli lead gung-gong drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.020.00032; Locke, David
    - Damba Mangli lead gung-gong drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.020.00033; Locke, David
    - Damba Mangli ensemble rhythm notation, 2010; MS122.002.020.00034; Locke, David
    - Damba Mangli drumming ensemble audio, live, 2008; MS122.002.020.00035; Agbekor Drum and Dance Society, Dagomba Section; Goldmann, Jonathan
    - Damba Mangli drumming ensemble audio, multitrack aggregate, 2005; MS122.002.020.00036; Lunna, Abubakari; Wasserman, Luke
    - Damba Mangli lead gung-gong vocables transcription, 2010; MS122.002.020.00037; Locke, David
    - Damba Mangli lead gung-gong drumming transcription, 2010; MS122.002.020.00038; Locke, David
    - Damba Mangli lead lunga drum language audio (1) balim, 2010; MS122.002.020.00039; Locke, David
    - Damba Mangli lead lunga drum language audio (2a) to naa wama, 2010; MS122.002.020.00040; Locke, David
    - Damba Mangli lead lunga drum language audio (2b) wama Damba, 2010; MS122.002.020.00041; Locke, David
    - Damba Mangli lead lunga drum language audio (3) wama wama wam' Damba, 2010; MS122.002.020.00042; Locke, David
    - Damba Mangli lead lunga drum language audio (4) wam' damba to ka wam' Damba, 2010; MS122.002.020.00043; Locke, David
    - Damba Mangli answer lunga drum language audio (1) Mohammedu, 2010; MS122.002.020.00044; Locke, David
    - Damba Mangli answer lunga drum language audio (2) damba dali m-bongo, 2010; MS122.002.020.00045; Locke, David
    - Damba Sochendi lead lunga drum language audio (1) To to to, 2010; MS122.002.020.00046; Locke, David
    - Damba Sochendi lead lunga drum language audio (2) Damba m-bongo, 2010; MS122.002.020.00047; Locke, David
    - Damba Sochendi lead lunga drum language audio (3) niri nuni nin ti ma, 2010; MS122.002.020.00048; Locke, David
    - Damba Sochendi lead lunga drum language audio (4) nyema nyema, 2010; MS122.002.020.00049; Locke, David
    - Damba Sochendi answer lunga drum language audio (1) naa wum naa wum naa wum, 2010; MS122.002.020.00050; Locke, David
    - Damba Sochendi answer lunga drum language audio (2) naa wum to naa wum to naa wum, 2010; MS122.002.020.00051; Locke, David
  - Baamaaya, group dance, 2001 -- 2010; MS122.002.021; 104 Digital Object(s)
    - Baamaaya-Baamaaya lead lunga vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.021.00001; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Baamaaya lead lunga vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.021.00002; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Baamaaya lead lunga drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.021.00003; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Baamaaya lead lunga drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.021.00004; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Baamaaya lead lunga drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.021.00005; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Baamaaya lead gung-gong vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.021.00006; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Baamaaya lead gung-gong vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.021.00007; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Baamaaya lead gung-gong drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.021.00008; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Baamaaya lead gung-gong drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.021.00009; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Baamaaya lead gung-gong drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.021.00010; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Baamaaya ensemble rhythm notation, 2010; MS122.002.021.00011; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Baamaaya drumming ensemble audio, live, 2008; MS122.002.021.00012; Agbekor Drum and Dance Society, Dagomba Section; Goldmann, Jonathan
    - Baamaaya-Baamaaya drumming ensemble audio, multitrack aggregate, 2005; MS122.002.021.00013; Lunna, Abubakari; Wasserman, Luke
    - Baamaaya-Dakoli Kutoko lead lunga vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.021.00014; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Dakoli Kutoko lead lunga vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.021.00015; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Dakoli Kutoko lead lunga drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.021.00016; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Dakoli Kutoko lead lunga drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.021.00017; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Dakoli Kutoko lead lunga drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.021.00018; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Dakoli Kutoko lead gung-gong vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.021.00019; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Dakoli Kutoko lead gung-gong vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.021.00020; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Dakoli Kutoko lead gung-gong drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.021.00021; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Dakoli Kutoko lead gung-gong drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.021.00022; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Dakoli Kutoko lead gung-gong drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.021.00023; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Dakoli Kutoko ensemble rhythm notation, 2010; MS122.002.021.00024; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Dakoli Kutoko drumming ensemble audio, live, 2008; MS122.002.021.00025; Agbekor Drum and Dance Society, Dagomba Section; Goldmann, Jonathan
    - Baamaaya-Dakoli Kutoko drumming ensemble audio, multitrack aggregate, 2005; MS122.002.021.00026; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Mazhe lead lunga vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.021.00027; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Mazhe lead lunga vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.021.00028; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Mazhe lead lunga drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.021.00029; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Mazhe lead lunga drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.021.00030; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Mazhe lead lunga drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.021.00031; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Mazhe lead gung-gong vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.021.00032; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Mazhe lead gung-gong vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.021.00033; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Mazhe lead gung-gong drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.021.00034; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Mazhe lead gung-gong drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.021.00035; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Mazhe lead gung-gong drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.021.00036; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Mazhe ensemble rhythm notation, 2010; MS122.002.021.00037; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Mazhe drumming ensemble audio, live, 2008; MS122.002.021.00038; Agbekor Drum and Dance Society, Dagomba Section; Goldmann, Jonathan
      There is no live recording for this piece.
    - Baamaaya-Mazhe drumming ensemble audio, multitrack aggregate, 2005; MS122.002.021.00039; Lunna, Abubakari; Wasserman, Luke
    - Baamaaya-Naa Daa lead lunga vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.021.00040; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Naa Daa lead lunga vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.021.00041; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Naa Daa lead lunga drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.021.00042; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Naa Daa lead lunga drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.021.00043; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Naa Daa lead lunga drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.021.00044; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Naa Daa lead gung-gong vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.021.00045; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Naa Daa lead gung-gong vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.021.00046; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Naa Daa lead gung-gong drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.021.00047; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Naa Daa lead gung-gong drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.021.00048; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Naa Daa lead gung-gong drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.021.00049; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Naa Daa ensemble rhythm notation, 2010; MS122.002.021.00050; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Naa Daa drumming ensemble audio, live, 2008; MS122.002.021.00051; Agbekor Drum and Dance Society, Dagomba Section; Goldmann, Jonathan
    - Baamaaya-Naa Daa drumming ensemble audio, multitrack aggregate, 2005; MS122.002.021.00052; Lunna, Abubakari; Wasserman, Luke
    - Nyagboli (Baamaaya) lead lunga vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.021.00053; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Nyagboli (Baamaaya) lead lunga vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.021.00054; Locke, David
    - Nyagboli (Baamaaya) lead lunga drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.021.00055; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Nyagboli (Baamaaya) lead lunga drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.021.00056; Locke, David
    - Nyagboli (Baamaaya) lead lunga drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.021.00057; Locke, David
    - Nyagboli (Baamaaya) lead gung-gong vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.021.00058; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Nyagboli (Baamaaya) lead gung-gong vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.021.00059; Locke, David
    - Nyagboli (Baamaaya) lead gung-gong drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.021.00060; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Nyagboli (Baamaaya) lead gung-gong drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.021.00061; Locke, David
    - Nyagboli (Baamaaya) lead gung-gong drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.021.00062; Locke, David
    - Nyagboli (Baamaaya) ensemble rhythm notation, 2010; MS122.002.021.00063; Locke, David
    - Nyagboli (Baamaaya) drumming ensemble audio, live, 2008; MS122.002.021.00064; Agbekor Drum and Dance Society, Dagomba Section; Goldmann, Jonathan
    - Nyagboli (Baamaaya) drumming ensemble audio, multitrack aggregate, 2005; MS122.002.021.00065; Lunna, Abubakari; Wasserman, Luke
    - Baamaaya-Baamaaya lead lunga vocables transcription, 2010; MS122.002.021.00066; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Baamaaya lead lunga drumming transcription, 2010; MS122.002.021.00067; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Baamaaya lead gung-gong vocables transcription, 2010; MS122.002.021.00068; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Baamaaya lead gung-gong drumming transcription, 2010; MS122.002.021.00069; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Dakoli Kutoko lead lunga vocables transcription, 2010; MS122.002.021.00070; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Dakoli Kutoko lead lunga drumming transcription, 2010; MS122.002.021.00071; Locke, David